Your lie lies on frozen lips
你的谎言在苍白的花瓣凋零之时
as pale petals 'bout to fall off.
摊在你那冰冻的嘴唇上
Hopefully I'll get used to this
希望我已经习惯
hoax that our lovemade.
这因爱而生的骗局
Wind whines through broken tips
风通过残破的废墟
as our memories die off.
泣诉著我们消亡的记忆
Hopefully you'll get used to my
希望你已经习惯
hugs - meaning good-bye.
拥抱象征着离别
Loves me, loves me not.
对我还有眷恋之情吗
Tried to get a rise out of
你锲而不舍地追问著
magnolia petals but
不久木兰花瓣
soon scattered them over you.
已经遍布了你的身旁
Watch me fall & drop away.
你眼睁睁看著我点点陨落
-Dropped me bad.
所以 不要再对我有任何眷恋之情了
Full of tears shall be stream
泪终将汇成河
Life ends up La cri mo sa
我的生命只成为一阵哭泣
Shattered heart, burnt my life out.
我破碎的心灵把我的生命烧尽
Why you still my remedy.
为什么你还是我的解药
Loves me, loves me not.
对我还有眷恋之情吗?
Tried to get a rise out of
你锲而不舍地追问著
magnolia petals but
不久木兰花瓣
soon scattered them over you.
已经遍布了你的身旁
Watch me fall & drop away.
你眼睁睁看著我点点陨落后缓缓离开
Drop me bad
所以请不要再对我有任何眷恋之情了
自私地把我抛弃
Drop me bad
无情地把我抛弃
Full of tears shall be stream
泪终将汇成河
Life ends up La cri mo sa
我的生命只成为一阵哭泣
Shattered heart,burnt my life out
你粉碎了我的心灵并把我的生命烧尽
Why you still my remedy
为什么你还是我的解药
Loves me, loves me not.
对我还有眷恋之情吗
Tried to get a rise out of
你锲而不舍地追问著
magnolia petals but
不久木兰花瓣
soon scattered them over you.
已经遍布了你的身旁
Watch me fall & drop away.
你眼睁睁看著我点点陨落后缓缓离开
Hear me cry,
听着我的哭声
Our love's dead dried.
只因我们的感情已终焉